forexforum.asia 2009-09-11

# Forex (FX) Forum .Asia | Currency Trading | The Social Network for Forex Traders - Privacy Policy

#### **Privacy Statement**

#### FOrex Forum .Asia recognizes the importance of your privacy and is committed to protecting any personal information about you, which we hold. This privacy policy describes how we manage your personal information and safeguard your privacy.

#### Collecting personal information about you

We only collect personal information that is necessary for us to perform our functions, and will only use or disclose this information for the purposes for which it was provided. These include providing you with your forum membership, mail outs and information about activities for members. Forex Forum .Asia may also survey some members in order to improve our services.

The personal information we collect and hold about you includes information you give us when you apply for a membership or complete an online form on our website. This will include your name, address, date of birth and contact details.

The only personal information which we collect about you when you use our website is what you tell us about yourself, for example, by completing an online form or by sending us an email. We will record your email address if you send us an email.

#### Using and disclosing your personal information

We respect your privacy. We will only use or disclose your personal information for the purpose for which you provided it to us, unless:

  * We have your consent; or
  * It is required or authorised by law.

####  **Public Forums**

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Choice / Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. At any point of time, you can unsubscribe from Forex Forum .Asia by [contacting us](http://www.forexforum.asia/sendmessage.php). 

#### Changes to our privacy policy

From time to time it may be necessary for us to review and revise our privacy policy. We will always publish an updated version on our Website.
